<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <color name="background">#964514</color>
    <string name="Archelon">Archelon</string>
    <string name="Archelon_Info">The Archelon is a species of extinct sea turtle known for being the largest of its kind ever documented. Contrary to most sea turtles,
the Archelon had a leathery shell, along with a pointed tail and narrow skull. Its diet minly consisted of mollusks, such as squid.</string>
    <string name="CB_Info">The Florida Cave Bear weighed about 650 pounds, roughly the size of a modern-day brown bear. It is charactedized by a dome shaped skull and a very
steep forehead. Its teeth are thought to have done more damage than other species of bear. The Cave Bear went extinct around 8,000 years ago.
</string>
    <string name="Casteriode">Casteriode</string>
    <string name="Casteriode_Info">The Casteroide is an ancient species of beaver known for being the largest beaver to ever exist. The creature is characterized by
its large, broad inscisors, and would remain underwater for extended periods of time. The extinction of the Casteriode was most likely caused by widespread
ecological restructuring.</string>
    <string name="Cave_Bear">Cave Bear</string>
    <string name="Dugong">Dugong</string>
    <string name="E_Evolution">Modern elephants are the last surviving descendants of of a common ancestor that split and evolved into other species, such as the Wooly Mammoth and Dugong.</string>
    <string name="Elephant">Modern Elephant</string>
    <string name="Horse">Horse</string>
    <string name="Horse_Info">Ancient three-toed horses were commonly found in Florida and were about the size of a dog. Most resided either in forests or praries. Many fossils
can still be found today.</string>
    <string name="Mastadon">Mastadon</string>
    <string name="Mastadon_Info">The Mastadon was a prehistoric elephant known for their low shoulders and string tusks. Their diet primarilt consisted of leaves and berries, but could also
be found grazing. The Mastadon went extint due to a mass extinction between eras.</string>
    <string name="Megalodon">Megalodon</string>
    <string name="Megatherium">Megatherium</string>
    <string name="Megatherium_Info">The Megatherium was a giant sloth, and at 20 feet tall was one of the largest mammals in history. They were herbivores, using their large claws
to strip leaves and bark. The Megatherium went extinct around 10,000 years ago due to human hunting and rapid climate change.</string>
    <string name="Phorusrhacidae">Phorusrhacidae</string>
    <string name="Phorusrhacidae_Info">The Phorusrhacidae was large flightless bird that existed from 62 million to 2.5 million years ago. They were carnivores, and their extiction was most
likely due to increasing competition from other carnivores.</string>
    <string name="STT_Info">The Saber-Toothed Tiger was ferocious prehistoric cat, whose canine teeth grew up to 7 inches and they could open
    their mouths up extremely wide. These cats were carnivores, which means their diet consisted of animals, such as woolly mammoths, sloths, and other large prey. They
    became extict 10,000 years ago due to climate change and hunting.
    </string>
    <string name="Saber_Toothed_Tiger">Saber Toothed Tiger</string>
    <string name="WM_Info">The Wooly Mammoth lived from 1.8 million to 11,000 years ago. They grew up to 11 feet and weighed around 6 tons, which is about the size of a modern-day
African elephant. Their diet was herbivourous, which means they ate only plant-based foods. Drastic climate change and hunting contributed to the extiction of these animals,
although one population was able to survive on Wrangel Island until 4,000 years ago. </string>
    <string name="Wooly_Mammoth">Wooly Mammoth</string>
    <string name="animal_info">Animal Name</string>
    <string name="animal_label">Animals</string>
    <string name="animal_menu_title">Animals</string>
    <string name="answer_1a">Saber Toothed Tiger</string>
    <string name="answer_1b">Mammoth</string>
    <string name="answer_1c">Penguin</string>
    <string name="answer_1d">Giant Sloth</string>
    <string name="answer_2a">fish</string>
    <string name="answer_2b">mammal</string>
    <string name="answer_2c">bird</string>
    <string name="answer_2d">dinosaur</string>
    <string name="answer_3a">3.5 million years ago</string>
    <string name="answer_3b">200 million years ago</string>
    <string name="answer_3c">450 million years ago </string>
    <string name="answer_3d">530 million years ago</string>
    <string name="answer_4a">bear</string>
    <string name="answer_4b">shark</string>
    <string name="answer_4c">sea turtle</string>
    <string name="answer_4d">monkey</string>
    <string name="answer_5a">3.5 million</string>
    <string name="answer_5b">2.6 million </string>
    <string name="answer_5c">450 thousand</string>
    <string name="answer_5d">937 thousand</string>
    <string name="answer_6a">Dinosaurs did not like the heat</string>
    <string name="answer_6b">Florida was underwater when dinosaurs lived</string>
    <string name="answer_6c">Florida was too far from where dinosaurs lived</string>
    <string name="answer_6d">Dinosaurs did not live in North America</string>
    <string name="answer_7a">mastodon</string>
    <string name="answer_7b">megalodon</string>
    <string name="answer_7c">sabre tooth tiger</string>
    <string name="answer_7d">tyrannasaurous rex</string>
    <string name="answer_8a">40</string>
    <string name="answer_8b">3.5 million</string>
    <string name="answer_8c">0</string>
    <string name="answer_8d">800</string>
    <string name="answer_9a">monkeys</string>
    <string name="answer_9b">alligators</string>
    <string name="answer_9c">crabs</string>
    <string name="answer_9d">whales</string>
    <string name="answer_false">False</string>
    <string name="answer_true">True</string>
    <string name="app_name">Prehistoric Florida</string>
    <string name="ar_button">AR</string>
    <string name="archelon_sh">I am the largest turtle to ever live. I used my large, powerful jaws to crush crustaceans and mollusks. I also lacked a hard shell. Which prehistoric animal am I?</string>
    <string name="back_label">Back</string>
    <string name="enter_label">Enter</string>
    <string name="evolution_button"/>
    <string name="finish_label">Finish</string>
    <string name="games_label">Games</string>
    <string name="games_menu_title">Games</string>
    <string name="home_label">Home</string>
    <string name="info_button"/>
    <string name="main_title">Prehistoric Florida</string>
    <string name="map_label">Map</string>
    <string name="megalodon_sh">My skeleton is made up of almost entirely cartilage. I can grow up to 60 feet and may have produced the strongest bitein the history of the planet, 5 times the bite force of a T. Rex. Which prehistoric animal am I?</string>
    <string name="next_label">Next</string>
    <string name="question_1">1. Which of these animals did not populate Florida?</string>
    <string name="question_10">10. The sea level was lower than present in prehistoric Florida.</string>
    <string name="question_2">2.  Which of these fossil types have not been found in Florida?</string>
    <string name="question_3">3. When did Florida form?</string>
    <string name="question_4">4.  Which of the following is the oldest Floridian vertebrae fossil?</string>
    <string name="question_5">5. The giant prehistoric shark Megalodon became extinct how many years ago?</string>
    <string name="question_6">6. Why are there no dinosaur fossils in Florida?</string>
    <string name="question_7">7. The most recent "prehistoric" animal to live in Florida is the</string>
    <string name="question_8">8. How many dinosaur fossils were found in Florida?</string>
    <string name="question_9">9. Which of these animals were in existance during the time of the dinosaurs?</string>
    <string name="reptile_sh">I am a fierce aquatic reptile, closely related to a Komodo dragon. Which animal(s) could I be?</string>
    <string name="scavenger_hunt_label"/>
    <string name="sea_level_label"/>
    <string name="size_comparison_button"/>
    <string name="tiger_sh">I am a cat, but not closely related to tigers, cats, or other modern cats. I have very long fangs used for subduing prey. My jaw can open up to 120 degrees. Which prehistoric animal am I?</string>
    <string name="trivia_label"/>
</resources>