<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="Archelon">Archelon</string>
    <string name="Archelon_Info">The Archelon is a species of extinct sea turtle known for being the largest of its kind ever documented. Contrary to most sea turtles,
the Archelon had a leathery shell, along with a pointed tail and narrow skull. Its diet minly consisted of mollusks, such as squid.</string>

    <string name="Wooly_Mammoth">Woolly Mammoth</string>
    <string name="WM_Info">The Woolly Mammoth lived from 1.8 million to 11,000 years ago. They grew up to 11 feet and weighed around 6 tons. Their diet was herbivourous, which means they ate only plant-based foods. Drastic climate change and hunting contributed to the extiction of these animals,
although one population was able to survive on Wrangel Island until 4,000 years ago. </string>

    <string name="Saber_Toothed_Tiger">Saber Toothed Tiger</string>
    <string name="STT_Info">The Saber Toothed Tiger was ferocious prehistoric cat, whose canine teeth grew up to 12 inches and whose mouth could openup to 120 degrees. These cats were carnivores, which means their diet consisted of animals, such as woolly mammoths, sloths, and other large prey. They
    became extict 10,000 years ago due to climate change and hunting.
    </string>

    <string name="Phorusrhacidae">Phorusrhacidae</string>
    <string name="Phorusrhacidae_Info">The Phorusrhacidae was large flightless bird that existed from 62 million to 2.5 million years ago. They were carnivores, and their extinction was most
likely due to increasing competition from other carnivores.</string>

    <string name="Megatherium">Megatherium</string>
    <string name="Megatherium_Info">The Megatherium was a giant sloth, and at 20 feet tall was one of the largest mammals in history. They were herbivores, using their large claws
to strip leaves and bark. The Megatherium went extinct around 10,000 years ago due to human hunting and rapid climate change.</string>

    <string name="Mastadon">Mastodon</string>
    <string name="Mastadon_Info">The Mastodon was a prehistoric elephant known for their low shoulders and string tusks. Their diet primarily consisted of leaves and berries, but could also
be found grazing. The Mastodon went extinct due to a mass extinction between eras.</string>

    <string name="Horse">Horse</string>
    <string name="Horse_Info">Ancient three-toed horses were commonly found in Florida and were about the size of a dog. Most resided either in forests or prairies. Many fossils
can still be found today.</string>

    <string name="Casteroide">Casteroide</string>
    <string name="Casteroide_Info">The Casteroide is an ancient species of beaver known for being the largest beaver to ever exist. The creature is characterized by
its large, broad inscisors, and would remain underwater for extended periods of time. The extinction of the Casteroide was most likely caused by widespread
ecological restructuring.</string>


    <string name="Cave_Bear">Cave Bear</string>
    <string name="CB_Info">The Florida Cave Bear weighed about 650 pounds, roughly the size of a modern-day brown bear. It is characterized by a dome shaped skull and a very
steep forehead. Its teeth are thought to have done more damage than other species\'. The Cave Bear went extinct around 8,000 years ago.
</string>

    <string name="Dugong">Dugong</string>


    <string name="Megalodon">Megalodon</string>
    <string name="Megalodon_Info">The Megalodon lived around 15.9-2.6 million years ago. These huge sharks were one of the largest predators in history, growing up to 50 feet long and weighing 114 tons. They were carnivores with very large teeth, and the name Megalodon lterally means "big tooth".</string>

    <string name="Elephant">Modern Elephant</string>
    <string name="E_Evolution">Modern elephants are the last surviving descendants of a common ancestor that split and evolved into other species, such as the Woolly Mammoth and Dugong.</string>


    <string name="horse">Horse</string>
    <string name="h_evolutioni">The modern horse has it roots in a dog-sized proto-horse that lived during the prehistoric times. The one-toed horse we know today had ancestors with three or four toes.</string>
</resources>